Guide to the KUHT Records 1997-006
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
- Photographs and Slides
  - #2336 Lawyer to Layman, Set Layout, photo: Dan Richardson, September 30, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 34)
  - #2318 Election Special, host: Susan Wright, photo: Dan Richardson, October 1, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 35)
  - #2332 The Public Times, Cover Shot, photo: Dan Richardson, October 1, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 36)
  - #2329 Fever Promo Slide, art: Bob Balazik, October 6, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 37)
  - #2344 Development Helicopter, photo: Dan Richardson, October 8, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 38)
  - #2349 Membership, Carol Kilpatrick, Peggy Sheffick, photo: Dan Richardson, October 9, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 39)
  - #2370 Rollie McGinnis, photo: Dan Richardson, October 10, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 40)
  - #2342 An Evening with Dickran Atamian, art: Dan Richardson, October 15, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 41)
  - #2391 ACT Awards, photo: Dan Richardson, October 23, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 42)
  - #2395 Election 1980, Set Photos, photos: Dan Richardson, October 23, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 43)
  - #2417 Membership, General Homes; Sesame St., November 5, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 44)
  - #2443 La Voz Special, photo: Dan Richardson, November 6, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 45)
  - #2442 La Voz Special, photo: Dan Richardson, November 15, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 46)
  - #2472 Auction Specials Party, photo: Dan Richardson, November 18, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 47)
  - #1980 November Membership Drive, photo: Bob Balazik, November 19, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 48)
  - #2483 Adoption in America, photo: Bob Balazik, November 26, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 49)
  - #2204 Auction Awards, photo: Dan Richardson, 1980 (Box 442, Folder 50)
  - #ID Material for KUHT, 1980-1981 (Box 442, Folder 51)
  - #1980 Set Designs of 1980 (Box 442, Folder 52)
  - #2674 Dick Cavette Show, photo: Dan Richardson, January 7, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 53)
  - #2674 Corporation for Public Broadcasting, Convention photo: Dan Richardson, January 7, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 54)
  - #64 Heartbreak Turtle, January 15, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 55)
  - #63 PTV Set for 1981, photo: Dan Richardson, January 15, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 56)
  - #69 Membership New Products, Mug, Bag, photo: Dan Richardson, January 21, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 57)
  - #114 U.S. Chronicles, photo: Dan Richardson, January 26, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 58)
    - U.S. Chronicles negatives (30), January 26, 1981
  - #108 Secret Service ID Photo, Staff Photos 1981, photo: Dan Richardson, January 30, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 59)
  - #100 1981 Auction Volunteer, photo: Tejas, February 3, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 60)
  - #142 1981 Auction Insert, photo: Dan Richardson, Bob Balazik, February 11, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 61)
  - #371 Valentines ID Slide, photo: Dan Richardson, February 13, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 62)
  - #373 Development Target Stores, photo: Dan Richardson, February 18, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 63)
  - #370 Friday Local, photo: Dan Richardson, February 20, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 64)
  - #324 Family - Musical Special, photo: Dan Richardson, February 21, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 65)
  - #456 La Voz, photo: Bob Balazik, February 26, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 66)
  - #466 Milt Larkins - Rhumboogie, photo: Dan Richardson, February 26, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 67)
  - #509 Curtain, photo: Bob Balazik, March 3, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 68)
  - #644 Membership Drive March, photo: Dan Richardson, March 18-22, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 69)
  - #458 Art Preview Party, photo: Dan Richardson, April 6, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 70)
  - #807 Development Gemcraft Homes, Bob Hutchins - President, Russ Hutchins - V.P., Frank Romero - V.P., Betty Lade - Ch.8, April 15, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 71)
  - #1013 Auction 1981, photo: Dan Richardson, April 30-May 9, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 72)
  - #840 Friday Local - Host: Shane Fox, photo: Dan Richardson, May 4, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 73)
  - #1024 Southern Gardening, photo: Dan Richardson, May 21, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 74)
  - #1137 Signing with Cindy, photo: Dan Richardson, D. Dale, June 3, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 75)
  - #1242 1982 Auction Chairman: Mary Faye Way, photo: Dan Richardson, July 7, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 76)
  - Children's Art Party, photo: D. Dale, August 19, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 77)
  - #1649 The Public Times: Public Housing October Times, photo: D. Dale, August 24, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 78)
  - Signing with Cindy, Color Transparencies, September 1, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 79)
  - #1651 Nightly Business Report, photo: D. Dale, September 10, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 80)
  - #1628 Volunteer Awards Party, September 30, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 81)
  - How to be a Financially Secure Woman, photo: D. Dale, October 1, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 82)
  - Watt James, Secretary of the Interior, photo: D. Dale, November 1981 (Box 442, Folder 83)
  - #1688 Friends Dinner, 1 color, 1 B&W, photo: D. Dale, November 5, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 84)
  - Where is Our Parade?, 1 color, 1 B&W, photo: D. Dale, November 12, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 85)
  - #397 Auction '81 Celebrity Showcase - Nancy Aimes, Caroll Ann, photo: Dan Richardson (Box 442, Folder 86)
  - Bathtub - JKE, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 87)
  - #1945 Celebration of the Harvest II, photo: D. Dale, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 88)
  - Greenroom, photo: D. Dale, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 89)
  - Houston Weekly, photo: D. Dale, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 90)
  - Membership Drive, Formal #3, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 91)
  - New Visions - Set Design, photo: D. Dale, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 92)
  - PBS Annual Conference, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 93)
  - Public Times - Elephant Race, December Cover Set-up, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 94)
  - Signing with Cindy, 1981 (Box 442, Folder 95)
  - #1674 Auction, photo: D. Dale, 1981-1982 (Box 442, Folder 96)
  - Auction Zip Code Luncheon, photo: D. Dale, 1981-1982 (Box 442, Folder 97)
  - ACT Board Meeting, photo: D. Dale, 1981-1982 (Box 442, Folder 98)
  - Membership Premiums, photo: D. Dale, 1981-1982 (Box 442, Folder 99)
  - Volunteers & ACT Board Members, Portraits - formal, candid, photo: D. Dale, 1981-1982 (Box 442, Folder 100)
  - Greenroom - Carol Channing, New Set, photo: D. Dale, January 4, 1982 (Box 442, Folder 101)
    - Carol Channing on The Greenroom negatives (31), January 4, 1982
  - Journey to the Sky, photo: D. Dale, January 13, 1982 (Box 442, Folder 102)
  - #2257 Elissa, photo: D. Dale, February 11, 1982 (Box 442, Folder 103)
    - Filming Elissa negatives (35), February 11, 1982
  - Journey to the Sky, February 12, 1982 (Box 442, Folder 104)
  - #1342 Bradshaw on..., photo: D. Dale, February 17, 1982 (Box 442, Folder 105)
  - Fritz Lieber, photo: D. Dale, April 1982 (Box 442, Folder 106)
    - Fritz Leiber negatives (30), April 1982
  - Auction '82 - During Auction Shots, April 22-May 1, 1982 (Box 442, Folder 107)
  - "Annie" Premier & Party Planning Shots, photo: D. Dale, May 1982 (Box 442, Folder 108)
  - The Dutch Connection, photo: D. Dale, June 2, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 1)
  - Rubenstein, Arthur, July 12, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 2)
    - Arthur Rubenstein photograph, July 12, 1982
    - Arthur Rubenstein photograph, July 12, 1982
  - For Sale: Houston, July 20, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 3)
  - Public Policy Forum - Gerald Ford, photo: D. Dale, July 21, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 4)
    - Gerald Ford on Public Policy Forum negatives (21), July 21, 1982
  - The Moneymakers - Venita Van Caspel, photo: D. Dale, July 30, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 5)
  - Victoria Campus, September 1982 (Box 443, Folder 6)
  - Ballet Party, Pam Baugh, Fred Gallatin, September 16, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 7)
  - HISD, October 1982 (Box 443, Folder 8)
  - Robert Brannon, October 1982 (Box 443, Folder 9)
  - Shoplifting Set, Production, October 21, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 10)
  - Porter and Company, photo: D. Dale, November 1982 (Box 443, Folder 11)
  - New Gospel Jubilee, photo: D. Dale, November 6, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 12)
  - Houston Businessman Colloquy, photo: D. Dale, November 11, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 13)
  - ACT Luncheon - Alan Shepard, photo: D. Dale, November 19, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 14)
  - Auction - Auction Begins, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 15)
  - Breakfast of the Gods, photo: D. Dale, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 16)
  - Facilities, photo: D. Dale, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 17)
  - George Adamson: the Most Endangered Species, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 18)
  - ID Slide Material, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 19)
  - Membership - New Computer, Membership Drive, photo: D. Dale, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 20)
  - Messiah, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 21)
  - Money Show, photo: D. Dale, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 22)
  - Nuevas Visiones, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 23)
  - Staff Photos, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 24)
  - Teleconferences, photo: D. Dale, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 25)
  - Territory - Set, People, photo: D. Dale, 1982 (Box 443, Folder 26)
  - Auction, 1982-1983 (Box 443, Folder 27)
  - Auction 1983, starting November 1982 All Inclusive, photo: D. Dale, 1982-1983 (Box 443, Folder 28)
  - Success: You Can Have it, photo: Beth Maldonado, January 10, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 29)
  - Engineer's Party, Las Brisas, photo: D. Dale, January 12, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 30)
  - Houston from the Air, Goodyear Blimp Flight, photos: D. Dale, N. Skipper, January 14, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 31)
  - #4576 Friends Dinner, photo: D. Dale, January 20, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 32)
  - #4679 Financially Secure Women 1983, photo: D. Dale, January 28, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 33)
  - Breakfast of the Gods: Nobel Prize, February 1983 (Box 443, Folder 34)
  - The Computer Show, February 1983 (Box 443, Folder 35)
  - #4577 Sesame Street Saturday, February 5, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 36)
  - Buffalo, Canebrakes, & Old Texas Love Songs, originally Singin' Texas, February 23, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 37)
  - ACT Open House, photos: JK Ellis, February 27, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 38)
  - American Journey Press Party, photo: D. Dale, March 23, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 39)
  - Auction Warehouse Party, photo: D. Dale, March 28, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 40)
  - Facilities - Davey Knodel with Remote Transmitter Link, CRT & Keyboard, April 1983 (Box 443, Folder 41)
  - Lawyer to Layman, April 1983 (Box 443, Folder 42)
  - Houston Historical Photos Copied, April 11, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 43)
  - Houston City Hall, photo: D. Dale, May 1983 (Box 443, Folder 44)
  - Softball Mascot & Team Photos, May 1983 (Box 443, Folder 45)
  - U.H. Victoria Campus Drilling Rig Simulator, photo: J. Zapalae, May 12, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 46)
  - Awards Ceremony 1983, photo: D. Dale, May 20, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 47)
  - Chemical People Teleconference, photo: D. Dale, May 27, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 48)
  - Rape Face to Face, June 1983 (Box 443, Folder 49)
  - #1100 Magic of Dance, June 8, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 50)
  - Reading Rainbow - Levar Burton, photo: D. Dale, June 22, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 51)
    - LeVar Burton/Reading Rainbow Event negatives (35), June 22, 1983
  - Facilities, June 29, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 52)
  - Madam Scandal, photo: D. Dale, July 1, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 53)
  - Harps of Gold, photo: D. Dale, July 18, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 54)
  - 30th Annual Ch. 8 Tennis Classic, photo: D. Dale, July 23, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 55)
  - River of Innocence, photo: D. Dale, August 16, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 56)
  - Hurricane Alicia Damage, August 17, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 57)
  - Bayou Banjos, photo: D. Dale, August 20, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 58)
  - ID Photos, October 1983 (Box 443, Folder 59)
  - Devin & Rhodes, F. Gallatin, October 8, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 60)
  - Dinner at Julia's, photo: D. Dale, October 14, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 61)
  - Bradshaw on... Holiday Specials, photo: D. Dale, October 20, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 62)
  - The Barn, October 24, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 63)
  - Auction '84 Specials Chairman, photo: D. Dale, October 25, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 64)
  - Sunrise/Sunset, October 27, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 65)
  - 1984 Auction Area Chairman, photo: D. Dale, November 29, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 66)
  - Advertising Department A/V Show, December 1983 (Box 443, Folder 67)
  - Membership Drive, December 1983 (Box 443, Folder 68)
  - ACT, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 69)
  - Auction, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 70)
  - Fun Run - 8 for 8 Fun Run, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 71)
  - Greenroom, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 72)
  - GRETA, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 73)
  - Membership Drive March, photo: D. Dale, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 74)
  - Miscellaneous Photos, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 75)
  - Staff, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 76)
  - Thirtieth Anniversary Parties, photo: D. Dale, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 77)
  - Volunteer Awards Party, photo: D. Dale, 1983 (Box 443, Folder 78)
  - ACT Board Members, photo: D. Dale, 1983-1984 (Box 443, Folder 79)
  - Territory, 1983-1984 (Box 443, Folder 80)
  - Set Photos - New Sets for 1983-1984 Season (Box 443, Folder 81)
  - A Baby, Maybe?, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 82)
  - Lighting Packing Case Photos, HMI Lights, February 1984 (Box 443, Folder 83)
  - Reflections of Houston, February 1984 (Box 443, Folder 84)
  - Houston Archives - Manual, May 27, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 85)
  - Family Fest '84, photos: D. Dale, June 1984 (Box 443, Folder 86)
  - Public Times Cover, July 1984 (Box 443, Folder 87)
  - Service Awards, photo: D. Dale, August 3, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 88)
  - Images of America, July 6, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 89)
  - Youth Views Party at HISD, July 17, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 90)
  - Auction 1985, Beginning September 1984 (Box 443, Folder 91)
  - Proposition #2, September 1984 (Box 443, Folder 92)
  - Heritage: Society and the Jews, September 13, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 93)
  - Child Sexual Abuse, September 19, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 94)
  - Volunteer Awards Party 1984, September 19, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 95)
  - Champagne Under Glass, September 23, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 96)
  - #1992 KUHF Sign-on, New XMTR, photo: D. Dale, October 12, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 97)
  - Breathing Easy, November 1, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 98)
  - 8 for 8 Fun Run, December 8, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 99)
  - Masterpiece Theater "The Jewel in the Crown", December 9, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 100)
  - #1457/1460 The Achievers - Marry De Motle, photo: FW Gallatin (Box 443, Folder 101)
  - ACT, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 102)
  - Auction, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 103)
  - Auction Banana Slides Negatives, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 104)
  - Auction Chairperson, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 105)
  - Camera 8, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 106)
  - City Scene, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 107)
  - Greenroom, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 108)
  - GRETA Slides, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 109)
  - Membership, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 110)
  - Membership Premiums, photo: D. Dale, 1984 (Box 443, Folder 111)
  - Miscellaneous Photos, 1984 (Box 444, Folder 1)
  - P.I. Displays, 1984 (Box 444, Folder 2)
  - SECA 1984 Contacts Only, Negatives are at SECA Headquarters (Box 444, Folder 3)
  - Staff, 1984 (Box 444, Folder 4)
  - Tennis Classic #2, 1984 (Box 444, Folder 5)
  - Channel 8 Tennis Classic, 1984 (Box 444, Folder 6)
  - Video Equipment Cabinet, 1984 (Box 444, Folder 7)
  - The Writer in Society, photo: D. Dale, 1984 (Box 444, Folder 8)
    - The Writer in Society: Maya Angelou, Bobbie Ann Mason, Donald Barthelme, John Barth negatives (25), 1984
  - Your Children/Our Children, 1984 (Box 444, Folder 9)
  - Greenroom 1984-1985 Season, September-December 1984 (Box 444, Folder 10)
  - HISD Set, 1984-1985 (Box 444, Folder 11)
  - One the Record Season, 1984-1985 (Box 444, Folder 12)
  - ID Slides, January 1985 (Box 444, Folder 13)
  - Sesame Saturday, February 1985 (Box 444, Folder 14)
  - Child at Risk, March 1985 (Box 444, Folder 15)
  - Dr. Who Copy Work, March 1985 (Box 444, Folder 16)
  - American Playhouse - Solomon Northup's Odyssey, April 1985 (Box 444, Folder 17)
  - Buffalo Bayou, April 1985 (Box 444, Folder 18)
  - GRETA, May 7, 1985 (Box 444, Folder 19)
  - ID Slide Material, August 1, 1985 (Box 444, Folder 20)
  - Membership, August 1, 1985 (Box 444, Folder 21)
  - Wine Tasting Committee, August 21, 1985 (Box 444, Folder 22)
  - Celebrate the Harvest, October 12, 1985 (Box 444, Folder 23)
  - ACT Board Members, New, November 1985 (Box 444, Folder 24)
  - Bradshaw, November 1985 (Box 444, Folder 25)
  - Camera 8, November 1985 (Box 444, Folder 26)
  - Turtles, December 1985 (Box 444, Folder 27)
  - Lone Star Preview Party, December 14, 1985 (Box 444, Folder 28)
  - Auction, 1985 (Box 444, Folder 29)
  - Greenroom, 1985 (Box 444, Folder 30)
  - Staff, 1985 (Box 444, Folder 31)
  - Greenroom, January 1986 (Box 444, Folder 32)
  - Membership, January 22, 1986 (Box 444, Folder 33)
  - Auction Go-Getters Party, January 29, 1986 (Box 444, Folder 34)
  - Woodstock, March 5, 1986 (Box 444, Folder 35)
  - Pride of Peace, March 17, 1986 (Box 444, Folder 36)
  - Ken Homs Chinese Cookery, April 18, 1986 (Box 444, Folder 37)
  - Tennis Classic, July 13, 1986 (Box 444, Folder 38)
  - Fire in the East: A Portrait of Robert Frank, July 16, 1986 (Box 444, Folder 39)
  - Ford, Dr. Margaret, September 1986 (Box 444, Folder 40)
  - The Africans, September 1986 (Box 444, Folder 41)
  - The Great Persuaders, September 1986 (Box 444, Folder 42)
  - Wine Auction, November 13, 1986 (Box 444, Folder 43)
  - ACT Board Members, November 20, 1986 (Box 444, Folder 44)
  - Annual Report, 1986 (Box 444, Folder 45)
  - Auction, 1986 (Box 444, Folder 46)
  - Awards and Emmy Photos, 1986 (Box 444, Folder 47)
  - For Pets' Sake, 1986 (Box 444, Folder 48)
  - ID Slides, 1986 (Box 444, Folder 49)
  - Membership Drives, 1986 (Box 444, Folder 50)
  - Staff, 1986 (Box 444, Folder 51)
  - Auction, 1986-1987 (Box 444, Folder 52)
  - Facilities - Lobby Decor, January 1987 (Box 444, Folder 53)
  - Worthum Theater Interiors with Susan Wright, February 13, 1987 (Box 444, Folder 54)
  - Membership Drive, March 1987 (Box 444, Folder 55)
  - Our World Submissions, May 1987 (Box 444, Folder 56)
  - Shamrock Hotel Demolition, May 1987 (Box 444, Folder 57)
  - Staff - Joseph Williams, July 15, 1987 (Box 444, Folder 58)
  - Psychiatry Today, August 17, 1987 (Box 444, Folder 59)
  - Great Chefs of the West, August 21, 1987 (Box 444, Folder 60)
  - Celebrate the Harvest, Drawing Winners, October 1987 (Box 444, Folder 61)
  - Staff Portraits, October 1987 (Box 444, Folder 62)
  - Dr. Who Dinner, photos: JK Ellis, November 27, 1987 (Box 444, Folder 63)
  - Black Gold Phoenix, December 1987 (Box 444, Folder 64)
  - ACT Annual Report, 1987 (Box 444, Folder 65)
  - Auction, 1987 (Box 444, Folder 66)
  - Facilities, 1987 (Box 444, Folder 67)
  - Holbein - The 7 Wives of Henry, 1987 (Box 444, Folder 68)
  - Miscellaneous Photos, 1987 (Box 444, Folder 69)
  - Nature Underwriters, 1987 (Box 444, Folder 70)
  - Presidential Debates - Democrats, file: Firing Line, 1987 (Box 444, Folder 71)
  - School Bus Safety, 1987 (Box 444, Folder 72)
  - Staff, 1987 (Box 444, Folder 73)
  - Vietnam Memorial Tour, 1987 (Box 444, Folder 74)
  - Hispanic Family, February 24, 1988 (Box 444, Folder 75)
  - Friends Dinner, March 1988 (Box 444, Folder 76)
  - Gutin, Howard CHMN C.P.B., August 25, 1988 (Box 444, Folder 77)
  - Fraud Documentary, December 23, 1988 (Box 444, Folder 78)
  - Auction, 1988 (Box 444, Folder 79-81)
  - Bayou Bend, 1988 (Box 444, Folder 82)
  - Houston Futures, 1988 (Box 444, Folder 83)
  - Made in America, 1988 (Box 444, Folder 84)
  - Miscellaneous Photos, 1988 (Box 444, Folder 85)
  - Staff, 1988 (Box 445, Folder 1)
  - Station PR Tour, 1988 (Box 445, Folder 2)
  - Tennis Cookbook Promo, 1988 (Box 445, Folder 3)
  - The Making of the Representative of Planet 8, 1988 (Box 445, Folder 4)
  - Window on the War, 1988 (Box 445, Folder 5)
  - Membership Drive, August 1989 (Box 445, Folder 6)
  - Membership Drive, December 1989 (Box 445, Folder 7)
  - Alamanac, 1989 (Box 445, Folder 8)
  - Arts Alive, 1989 (Box 445, Folder 9)
  - Auction, 1989 (Box 445, Folder 10)
  - Buffalo Hardware, 1989 (Box 445, Folder 11)
  - Christmas, 1989 (Box 445, Folder 12)
  - Mayoral Debates, 1989 (Box 445, Folder 13)
  - Membership March, 1989 (Box 445, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Photos, 1989 (Box 445, Folder 15)
  - Staff, 1989 (Box 445, Folder 16)
  - TV History, 1989 (Box 445, Folder 17)
  - Membership Drive, March 1990 (Box 445, Folder 18)
  - Almanac, 1990 (Box 445, Folder 19-20)
  - Arts Alive, 1990 (Box 445, Folder 21)
  - Auction, 1990 (Box 445, Folder 22-23)
  - Board Members, 1990 (Box 445, Folder 24)
  - Community, 1990 (Box 445, Folder 25)
  - Community - Szechuan Dancers, 1990 (Box 445, Folder 26)
  - Computer Grid Laptop, 1990 (Box 445, Folder 27)
  - Fotofest Pix, 1990 (Box 445, Folder 28)
  - Golf Tournament, 1990 (Box 445, Folder 29)
  - Living with AIDS, 1990 (Box 445, Folder 30)
  - Tennis Classic, 1990 (Box 445, Folder 31)
  - Territory, 1990 (Box 445, Folder 32)
  - Town Meeting - HPD, 1990 (Box 445, Folder 33)
  - Staff, 1990-1991 (Box 445, Folder 34)
  - Town Meeting, March 1991 (Box 445, Folder 35)
  - Town Hall - Education, March 1991 (Box 445, Folder 36)
  - ACT Board, 1991 (Box 445, Folder 37)
  - The Challenge of Grief, 1991 (Box 445, Folder 38)
  - Community, 1991 (Box 445, Folder 39)
  - Facilities - Aerial Shots, 1991 (Box 445, Folder 40)
  - Golf Tournament, 1991 (Box 445, Folder 41)
  - JD's Journal, 1991 (Box 445, Folder 42)
  - Space Watch, 1991 (Box 445, Folder 43)
  - Spotlight Showcase, 1991 (Box 445, Folder 44)
  - Tenneca Marathon, 1991 (Box 445, Folder 45)
  - The Territory, 1991 (Box 445, Folder 46)
  - Wetlands, 1991 (Box 445, Folder 47)
  - Wildman, 1991 (Box 445, Folder 48)
  - ACT, 1991-1992 (Box 445, Folder 49)
  - Almanac, 1991-1992 (Box 445, Folder 50)
  - Community, 1991-1992 (Box 445, Folder 51)
  - Staff, 1991-1992 (Box 445, Folder 52)
  - The Territory, August 1992 (Box 445, Folder 53)
  - The American Soap Box Derby, 1992 (Box 445, Folder 54)
  - Community - Olympic Hopefuls, 1992 (Box 445, Folder 55)
  - JD's Journal, 1992 (Box 445, Folder 56)
  - Out of Work, 1992 (Box 445, Folder 57)
  - Staff Photo Group Shot, 1992 (Box 445, Folder 58)
  - Town Meeting - Aging, 1992 (Box 445, Folder 59)
  - Town Meeting - Our Children, 1992 (Box 445, Folder 60)
  - ACT Board People (Box 445, Folder 61)
  - Against all Odds, Set Design, photo: D. Dale (Box 445, Folder 62)
  - Almanac (Box 445, Folder 63)
  - Ames, Nancy, Agency photo, undated (Box 445, Folder 64)
  - Apollo 17 (Box 446, Folder 1)
    - Apollo 17 Interview negatives (35), undated
  - Archive Copies (Box 446, Folder 2)
  - Art of this Earth (Box 446, Folder 3)
  - Art Preview Party (Box 446, Folder 4)
  - Art T-Shirt Artwork (Box 446, Folder 5)
  - Auction Bid Board (Box 446, Folder 6)
  - Auction Promotion (Box 446, Folder 7)
  - A Baby Moves?, photo: Lisa Stewart (Box 446, Folder 8)
  - Bag Liwix (Box 446, Folder 9)
  - Bats (Box 446, Folder 10)
  - Bayou City Drag Racing (Box 446, Folder 11)
  - Bayou City Moto-X (Box 446, Folder 12)
  - Bean, Alan (Box 446, Folder 13)
  - Black Business Documentary, photo: D. Dale (Box 446, Folder 14)
  - Black Family Portrait (Box 446, Folder 15)
  - Black Heritage Gallery (Box 446, Folder 16)
  - Boy Scout Jamboree (Box 446, Folder 17)
  - Leo Buscaglia (Box 446, Folder 18)
  - Business Art Fund (Box 446, Folder 19)
  - Business Pilot (Box 446, Folder 20)
  - Center Stage (Box 446, Folder 21)
  - Channel 8 - Night at the Aeros (Box 446, Folder 22)
  - Child Abuse: The Perfect Crime (Box 446, Folder 23)
  - Copy Work Various Programs (Box 446, Folder 24)
  - Coreta Dale (Box 446, Folder 25)
  - The Cotton Exchange Building, Paul Yeager (Box 446, Folder 26)
  - Cranes, Flags (Box 446, Folder 27)
  - #1734 Development Award - Monty Levine, Dr. Florence Monroe, Yvonne Menuet, photo: D. Dale (Box 446, Folder 28)
  - Dirty Business (Box 446, Folder 29)
  - Dollars and Sense (Box 446, Folder 30-31)
  - Duets for Cannibals (Box 446, Folder 32)
  - Eco-Burnout: Houston, photo: D. Dale (Box 446, Folder 33)
  - Facilities (Box 446, Folder 34)
  - Facilities - Carport Demolition (Box 446, Folder 35)
  - For All Mankind Screening (Box 446, Folder 36)
  - Fotofest (Box 446, Folder 37)